Are you sure
Nawaam is really headed for Hy Izlan?
Yep. at least that's where
we were told to rendezvous.
But not sure how we're gonna
go about this alone.
Nawaam's army is too big
for you to take on by yourself.
It doesn't matter.
If Nawaam's going to be there.
then my father will be too.
We'll figure it out afterwards.
You're making a "I'm gonna
fight him alone" face.
That's very bold.
This is where it all started.
Who's there?
Zhima. is that you?
Master Zhima. you made it.
I'm glad to see that you also made it.
Four-Nines!
What a pleasant surprise.
I didn't expect you to bring Kwana.
Well. of course.
I was ultimately convinced
after Juro handed me this.
Hmm.
Pleasure to make your acquaintance.
My name is Homen.
I am a masterless Jedi.
like Ethan and Kwana.
Well. I appreciate you joining us today.
Huh?
I'm spotting a lot of ships
coming out of hyperspace right now.
Is it Nawaam's army?
No. Uh...
Come in.
Do you read me?
This is the Bibin Defense Fleet.
We heard you could use
some extra firepower.
Lady Tafflah!
Sorry to keep everyone waiting.
It took us a while
to rally all the troops.
Hmm?
Has Nawaam attacked?
Oh. my. Here comes
a little latecomer to the party.
And who could that be?
This is Lah Kara.
Is my father. Lah Zhima. there?
Kara!
I don't believe it...
Kara...
Oh. thank goodness.
I missed you so much.
Hmm?
No! Father! Wait!
Honestly. if you cut me down
right now. I wouldn't blame you.
It would just be a tad unfortunate.
seeing I'm currently
under your daughter's employ.
It's the truth.
A lot has happened since you've been gone.
but basically. what he really wants to do
right now is fight for what is right.
and now he's ready to fight alongside us.
You believe me now?
The color of your lightsaber
tells me all I need to know.
Hmm.
I'm sorry for everything. Kara.
There are still so many things
I have yet to tell you about.
It's okay.
I think I understand now.
She knows.
Why'd you keep it a secret?
We would've understood.
You're right.
When I think about it.
I never really was alone.
That reminds me...
I believe that this belongs to you.
And I have something for you.
It's yours. right?
Uh...
And this last lightsaber is for you.
Thank you. but I don't believe
I'm qualified to accept it.
You're wrong. you absolutely do.
Besides. I'm sure
this is what Juro would've wanted.
- Uh...
- Hmm.
Uh...
Hmm.
So. this must be the birth of the
new Jedi Order that Juro once dreamt of.
Huh?
I never wanted for you
to have to walk down this path. Kara.
Did you strike someone down?
Yes.
But take it from me.
for what it's worth.
your daughter is really strong.
I mean. she's up there
with the strongest Jedi I've faced.
She would be.
But despite all of your strength.
I would've never chosen
a Jedi's life for you.
There are times when a Jedi
must make heartbreaking choices.
It isn't easy to make such decisions.
And being strong doesn't mean
you will automatically be standing
on the right side of justice.
I've learned that.
But then. how else are we supposed
to help those who are in need?
That's a question
I have yet to find an answer to.
But there's more to it than just strength.
Otherwise. we would be
no different from Nawaam.
If it wasn't for what happened that day.
he might've become a great Jedi.
Not... From Nawaam...
I mean. I guess.
But what was he like?
You knew Nawaam. right?
He was just a youngling when Reno
tried to bring back the Jedi Order.
That day. when I chose
to take the wrong path. he was there.
and he became convinced
that it was the right one.
So. you see. I am the one
who turned him into a monster.
Oh. stay sharp. everyone.
It looks like our guest of honor's
just arrived.
It appears that they
got the jump on us somehow.
They're still no more
than a disorganized mess.
Indeed.
And that much easier to crush.
Activate the tractor beam.
And bring in the kyber crystal.
We're being pulled in.
Our allies bought us time
and slowed them down.
but it was just a matter of time.
All of you are going to have to attack
the fortress from the outside.
Father. what about you?
I have to stay here
and defend the crystal.
That's why I came here in the first place.
We cannot allow Nawaam
to get his hands on that crystal.
Because they are unprepared
for the consequences
that will happen if they use that thing.
What do you mean?
This crystal's purity grade is too high.
The power that would
come from something this size
would make it impossible to control.
Imagine daring to put a crystal like this
inside a cannon of that magnitude.
It won't just obliterate its target...
Everything in its line of fire.
from here to the edge of the galaxy.
will be wiped from existence.
So the fate of the galaxy is resting
on the outcome of our little battle.
Well. then I'm going out
for a spin.
I'll leave the rest to you.
You two should go and join
the defense fleet.
and attack Nawaam's fortress
from the outside.
I'm not leaving you. Father!
You must.
I have to do this alone.
If something were to happen.
I need to know that you'll survive.
But. I...
If the worst comes to pass out there.
promise me you'll run.
Choose an honest life.
not a glorious death.
Hmm.
May the Force be with you.
- Come on.
- Uh...
Bhozn. you will be
in charge of handling the enemy fleet.
Do not fail again.
And what will you be doing?
I'll be retrieving
the kyber crystal...
with your permission.
Yes.
Does it seem odd to you
that Gennoh would rather retrieve
a crystal than lead this battle?
He's not seeking a crystal.
but rather. revenge.
Revenge?
Attention all vessels.
Our target is the enemy fortress's
power center!
Hit 'em with everything you've got!
The rest of you.
support the Meteorite Fleet!
Draw the enemy this way!
The fate of the galaxy
depends on this battle.
Everyone's future is in your hands.
Listen up. you brutes!
I don't want a single one of their ships
able to reach Fort Dominion!
I knew you'd be here. Lah Zhima.
Wait. we have to turn around now!
But why?
My father's in danger!
I can sense it.
Kara!
Well. I guess we have no choice
but to turn back around too.
Agreed.
All righty.
Listen. You cannot use
this temple's crystal as a weapon.
You will not be able
to control what it does.
What of it?
I don't care what happens.
All I care about is defeating you.
Fine. As you wish.
So. you're using your new upgrades
to track my moves.
Precisely. but there's more...
Let's see how you do
against these upgrades!
Father!
Kara. why did you come back?
If I were you. I'd stay focused!
Watch out!
Now what? Lightsabers
and blasters don't work on that thing.
Forget about saving Zhima.
at this rate. we won't even
be able to save ourselves.
That's not true.
What do you mean?
Take a closer look.
See the shield?
I think it's having trouble
maintaining it.
which means our attacks
are doing some damage.
So. at that power level.
it can't keep its shield
deployed constantly.
Okay. But how do we take that thing down?
Something's wrong out there.
We have to wrap this up and help them.
Uh. Kara?
Despite
all of your Jedi training.
you can't outmatch
my speed with this body.
And this time. I will defeat you.
How foolish.
Oh. no!
Hmm.
This is bad.
They have the crystal.
I'd scold you for coming back.
but we do not have the time.
Listen.
You must do everything you can
to destroy the kyber cannon.
They cannot be allowed to use it.
What about you?
I'll find Nawaam so I can end this.
once and for all.